

I'm Vincent Orback, a freelancing web designer and frontend developer from Stockholm, Sweden.

I have an interest in both design and technology which makes for a great combination when working as a web designer. After studying system development and computer science I quickly moved towards the web to work more with design and user experiences. Since then I've worked at different agencies but right now I'm freelancing again, making websites for people, organizations and companies that I like, around the world.

When I'm not working with clients I like to work on side projects and open-source tools to keep me up to date with new tech and possibilities.

## **VINCENT ORBACK**

vorback@gmail.com | +46 725 309 222 | vincentorback.se

## **Experience**

Freelancing Web designer and developer

Aug 2015 - Now

Daytona Communications Front-end developer

Oct 2013 - Jun 2015

Queensbridge Front-end developer

Mar - Sep 2013

Traffic Light Developer (internship)

Dec 2012

## **Education**

Södertörn University
Philosophy A
2015-2016, Stockholm, Sweden
Philosophy B

Luleå University of Technology Script languages

2012, Remote

Malmö University Computer Science

2011 - 2012, Malmö, Sweden System development

Web development 1 Web development 2

Motion pictures

Södertörn University English A

2011, Stockholm, Sweden

Riddarfjärdens Gymnasium Graphic design & journalism

2011, Stockholm, Sweden